[theme music playing]
[laughs]
[Helena] She's so pathetic.
Look at her. Bye!
[Lily] You just let her escape!
She's gone!
You know, Agent Salonga,
I'd be careful if I were you.
I think my suspicions are correct.
There's a snake among us.
What's the latest update on Red Dragon?
[Romulo] We've retrieved
the pickup that rescued her.
It's been secured downstairs.
We're tracking down its owner.
[Lily] The pickup that attacked us
while Red Dragon was escaping
is registered under
one of your businesses.
[Lily] You aren't going to hell
just yet, Asuncion.
The Big Four want to set a meeting.
Big Four? And who the hell are they?
They are the four leaders of
Red Dragon's operations
in the north, south, east,
and west areas of the country.
Shouldn't we be talking about
who's going to replace Red Dragon?
It's quite obvious that I should take
Red Dragon's place
since I'm her only daughter.
Why don't we have an election?
Emilia versus me
for Red Dragon's position.
[Lily] If you're not with Red Dragon,
then you work for another group
that helped her escape.
[Agent Asuncion] You can't stop Red Dragon
because she's already left the country.
While Mama Dragon is away,
I want my baby dragon to slay.
[Emilia] The queen is back.
[chuckles]
Macau, Hong Kong, Taiwan.
If Red Dragon has really
left the Philippines,
she could have fled to one
of those three destinations.
Places in the north.
Nearby places which are easy to get to.
It's also alleged to be the headquarters
of a huge network of an Asian triad.
Triad?
I could be wrong about this,
which is why we must
study this more thoroughly
before involving foreign intelligence
in Red Dragon's case.
Never mind.
I have a spy in Red Dragon's organization.
We can keep track of their every move.
And hopefully, that'll help us
take down Red Dragon herself.
[tense music playing]
Like I said before.
My hunch about Diego was right.
Take a look.
[unsettling music playing]
[grunts]
[groaning]
[yells]
Arnaldo, calm down.
What's happening to you?
Look at me! Look at me! What did you see?
Ivy. Ivy. Ivy. Ivy!
Ivy…
Here, Arnaldo, take your medicine.
I don't need that!
Arnaldo.
[panting]
You take your medicines
because you need to get well.
Especially now that I've been reinstated
as the governor of our province.
Do you know what that means?
I need you to get well
so that you can take my place
once I step down!
You are going to assume
my place as governor,
so get your act together!
I'm sorry.
Sorry, Grandpa.
Doctor.
Will you please explain to me
what's happening to my grandson?
At this point, his memories
are all rushing back,
flooding his mind.
He remembers things from his past,
and at the same time, he also
remembers recent events.
He remembers being
devotional and religious.
It's all rushing back to him.
I do not need a grandson
who is a half-wit, half-sane, half-crazy,
half-man-of-God, half-
I don't know what anymore!
What I need is Arnaldo, the old Arnaldo!
The Arnaldo I brought up,
the Arnaldo I trained.
The Mayor Arnaldo
who's ruthless and cunning.
Yes, Governor.
But this is difficult for Arnaldo.
His mind has to sort out
all these memories.
Please, have some more patience.
Patience?
Patience is a virtue for the poor
because they have no choice
but to be patient with
the sorry state they're in!
I just got reinstated as
the governor of this province,
and you ask me to be patient?!
Cure my grandson!
Papa.
And you.
You're also testing me.
If you haven't been trying so hard
to become the leader
of your mother's group,
you would've known how pitiful
your son's condition is!
Doctor Go is the best
psychiatrist in town, Papa!
And please, let me correct you,
I am not desperate,
because Mama told me
that I'd be replacing her.
Didn't you tell me before
to seize the power?
Well, so I did!
Big deal!
You're being toyed with.
You know what the truth is?
If you truly want to lead her group,
if you want them to see you
as someone powerful,
you have to kill those four big
shots your mother works with!
Then, and only then,
will you have true power.
Then, and only then, will you
be recognized as a leader.
Without that, you're nothing.
You're just a figurehead.
This is not a game, Emilia!
Didn't you challenge me before
to look for evidence
that would prove you're a spy?
Well, there you go.
That's evidence enough, I'd say.
What's all this?
Seriously?
Are you trying to test my patience?
-Am I?
-Are you?
Both of you stop it.
Diego, take a seat.
Sit down.
So, what do you have to say for yourself?
What does it look like?
I was just organizing the documents.
Really now?
Well, hand me your phone then.
[tense music playing]
What's holding you back now?
You're hiding something, aren't you?
Let me remind you that unlike you,
I am not one of Red Dragon's goons.
I am her ally, and that
was what we agreed upon.
You can't treat me as if I'm some goon.
Unless I'm certain of your loyalty, Diego,
I cannot just trust you blindly.
Take him to the other room, and
don't take your eyes off him.
I can go there myself.
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
Give me that.
Once I prove that
Torillo's a spy, I'll kill him.
[suspenseful music playing]
I'm worried that
Mercedes has Diego's phone.
I've been trying to contact him
all day, but he's not answering.
Then I have to delete all
your messages to each other.
I hope nothing bad happens to Diego.
I need to talk to him.
I need to know if he's okay.
But how?
Maybe I can help.
Where's Diego? I'll go to him.
Damian, Diego's in a difficult position.
It's impossible for you to help.
But I can try.
He's at Red Dragon's base.
Do you know where that is?
I used to be in a gang
with Red Dragon's former men.
I'll find a way to give him your message.
No, you might just get in danger.
I can take care of myself.
I'll do anything to help you.
[whistles]
Your aura's different today, Emilia.
It's like you're very powerful.
You have such a strong appeal.
-Do I?
-Yeah.
You know, I heard your
conversation with your Papa.
Don't think about it.
I am different from your father.
I'm proud of you.
By the way, about your Mama's business…
Turns out, she's more than just a jeweler.
True enough, I was right.
Helena Montoya is Red Dragon.
And now, you're Baby Dragon.
Can you imagine that? That's so great!
You know, Raul, if you're sucking up to me
so you can be part of our organization,
you gotta stop right now.
How come?
[scoffs] Because it's a gangster world
and you won't fit in.
Wow. Gangster world.
Emilia, in case you've forgotten,
I run all of your father's
illegal businesses here.
Alone.
Raul, if I'm going to have
a business partner,
it should be the fake Jaguar,
because he's very manly
and he's the king of the underworld.
I am the queen, so I need a king.
But since you're funny,
you could be the… joker.
[chuckles]
Joker, huh?
Did you know that Emilia
is replacing Red Dragon?
What?!
You're telling me that Emilia
is taking her mother's place?
-Yes.
-Are you serious?
What's wrong with that?
Emilia is my nemesis.
She can't win over me again.
That can't happen.
You have to teach me the ropes.
Teach me everything I need
to know about the syndicate.
I need to win when I face Emilia again.
Please!
Okay.
Stop!
-Why?
-I'm serious!
You know what?
A beautiful woman like you
shouldn't be working.
You should just be worshipped
by men like me.
That or you just see me as a sex kitten.
I'm not a toy! I'm a woman!
And I have a brain.
A big one, in fact.
So get out!
Get out? I own this place.
I don't care if this is your place.
This is my room, so get out.
I said get out!
Okay, okay. Fine.
Get out!
Hurry!
[grunts]
[suspenseful music playing]
Leave us. I need to speak
with Diego in private.
You can't do that.
Mercedes said Diego can't talk to anyone
without her permission.
[scoffs]
Let me just remind you where you stand.
This is you, and this is me.
Who's on top?
Me.
Who gives the orders? I do.
So, you three get out.
Have some coffee or snacks,
or take a dip in the swimming pool.
Out.
-As you wish, sir.
-There we go.
Read this.
What's this?
-Where's this from?
-It's from Lily.
Pick out every tenth word in the article
to get Lily's message.
HOW ARE YOU?
JEPOY HAS ERASED OUR MESSAGES
ON THE CELL PHONE
IN CASE THEY CONFISCATE IT FROM YOU.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
How did you get this?
No questions. What matters
is you can talk to Lily.
If you want to tell her anything…
…write it here.
[suspenseful music playing]
Yes, Natalie.
You're reduced to this.
Dating an older man for power.
You and I both know
that you only want one man.
[tense music playing]
[phone chimes]
[soft music playing]
I LOVE ANNA.
[phone chimes]
-I LOVE ANNA.
-What?!
Ew.
That's weird.
You want me, you don't want me…
You want me!
Torillo pulled a fast one on us again!
He couldn't have deleted
the files on this phone!
That guy is a traitor!
Believe me, Mercedes!
We can't do anything to Diego
without any solid proof.
We'll answer to Red Dragon
if she finds out you're picking on him.
She still has some use for Diego,
so lay off him for now.
[unsettling music playing]
You have something that's mine?
[tense music playing]
Is everyone ready?
Okay, great.
As you can see,
I am well, alive, and kicking.
And while I'm away,
I am entrusting my position
to my baby girl.
My Baby Dragon…
Emilia Ardiente-Torillo.
To my Dragon Team,
be good to my Baby Dragon
if you don't want to be burnt to a crisp.
Goodbye.
[clapping]
Now that you've heard Red Dragon's message
that I'll be taking her place
while she's away,
does anyone want to say anything?
Mercedes?
Anyway, I'm inviting everyone for dinner.
I'm also inviting the Big Four.
Including you, Mercedes.
You're free to join us.
I told you, didn't I?
This throne suits me better than you.
Right, Mercedes?
I think you'd prefer that I keep quiet
than hear what I have to say.
But, you know, Mercedes?
I am willing to listen
to what you want to say.
I was raised by Red Dragon.
I grew up seeing that she
always made the right decision.
Except for now.
How can I respect an ex-politician,
a good-for-nothing Ardiente,
who's taking the place of the woman
I've idolized almost all my life?
You are not my queen,
and you will never be.
I'd rather die than kneel before you.
[groaning]
Emilia!
[gasping]
[Mercedes coughing]
-[groans]
-[grunts]
-[coughing]
-Vanessa.
-You know what to do with her.
-Yes, Madam.
[grunts] Stop! Let go of me!
[grunts]
How dare you, Emilia?!
I'll have my revenge! Remember that!
Let go! [gasping]
I said let go!
I'm giving everyone in this
room the opportunity to tell me
whatever they want in front of my face.
But don't you ever dare
question my capabilities
or belittle my name
the way that woman did!
I've learned many things
from being the mayor
and governor of this town.
And don't you ever dare think
that I became the leader of this faction
just because I'm Red Dragon's daughter!
Is that clear?
Good.
[ominous music playing]
You may all go.
[groaning, grunting]
[suspenseful music playing]
[tense music playing]
Thank you, Doctor. You can go now.
Hi.
[moans]
Take it easy. You were beat up pretty bad.
Don't tell me you just
happened to be there
when Emilia threw me out.
And don't tell me you're
just a good Samaritan.
[scoffs]
We know each other very well, Lily Cruz.
Are we still going to
beat around the bush?
I don't like playing games.
I want you to be part of my group.
I want you to leave Red Dragon
so you can get back at Emilia.
Once they press charges
against Red Dragon,
you will testify against her.
[chuckling]
Yes, yes, Mercedes. Yes.
It might seem funny now.
But before you know it,
we'll be on the same side.
So, what do you think?
Are you going to join my group or…
Do you want to play
second fiddle to Emilia forever?
Hi, love.
Anna.
Come on. I bought some bread. Let's eat.
Oh! Sorry.
Come on, Jepoy. Let's eat.
I bought a lot of bread.
Choose what you want.
Come on, love.
My girlfriend is so sweet.
Of course.
Hold on.
Are you okay?
Why do you look distracted? Huh?
[sensual music playing]
Stop it.
[gasps] Jepoy!
Cut it… Jepoy! Stop!
Jepoy? Anna?
Anna.
[soft tense music playing]
Hey.
Thanks, but no thanks.
Wow.
Unbelievable.
You're still loyal to them.
Even though they treat you like trash.
I'm only loyal to myself.
I'm nobody's pet.
I just saved your life.
And I thank you for that.
Just add it to my long list of debts
because I'll be sure to pay you back.
[chuckles]
Prideful, aren't you, Mercedes?
I only know my self-worth.
But you don't know your value.
Emilia is born to lead your faction,
but you are made to rule.
You deserve better.
And you will see that
once you join my group.
I'd much rather be alone
than become your little pet.
You just made the biggest
mistake of your life, Mercedes.
Now get some rest.
Maybe once you're all healed up,
you'll finally be able
to make rational decisions.
[unsettling music playing]
[soft music playing]
Don't you want to have coffee first?
Jepoy.
[soft dramatic music playing]
Natalie, this is for you.
What's that?
-A bribe?
-[chuckles]
I have my own laptop, thank you very much.
That laptop contains everything you need
to know about the southern faction.
Isn't that what you wanted?
To learn everything you can
about the syndicate?
-And you're giving it to me?
-Of course!
Because I want you to be happy.
And don't worry.
Someday, all this will be yours.
Even my men.
You two, come here.
Tell your comrades that from now on,
you will obey all of Natalie's orders.
-Is that clear?
-Yes, boss.
Okay. Go, go. Go!
Don't you want it?
Are you happy?
Yes, Daddy.
This has everything?
[chuckles]
Everything you need.
[ominous music playing]
Thank you, Daddy.
Emilia and Red Dragon's group
are planning a huge meeting.
But we don't know what
the exact time and location are.
It could be the perfect chance
to arrest them.
Arrest?
Emilia and the Big Four.
And if we succeed,
we'll be able to take down
the entire syndicate.
I'll talk this over with Agent Salonga.
What about Mercedes?
Do you think she'll attend?
What if she rats you out to Emilia?
She wouldn't dare let them
call her a traitor,
so I know she won't, Mom.
[tense music playing]
I've received the contracts
you sent me, Mr. Castro.
Let me just review them,
then I'll get back to you.
Thank you.
Thanks for letting me
stay here again, Lily.
I realized I still have so many books here
for the kids at the Sitio.
You're welcome here anytime, Anna.
You know that, right?
By the way, where's Jepoy?
Why isn't he with you?
He could've helped you out.
What's the matter? Did you fight?
No, Lily. We didn't.
Well, that's what it looks like to me.
[Natalie] Good morning, hot stuff.
[sexy music playing]
Ma'am, what are you doing here?
-Good morning, Lily.
-Good morning, Anna.
Hey, Marlon.
Marlon can go with you to Sitio Onse.
-Can you accompany Anna?
-Sure.
Take care, Anna.
Thanks, Lily.
-Marlon.
-Sure.
Are these books good to go?
Let's sort them out.
[soft music playing]
-I missed you.
-Ma'am.
Ma'am, we've already talked about this.
I know, but I'm trying…
I'm trying to move on.
I really missed you.
Ma'am.
I'm dating someone new.
And…
He's a bit older than me,
but he's very powerful.
He's actually part of
Red Dragon's Big Four.
-Big Four?
-Mm-hmm.
I don't really want to talk
about him right now.
I came to see you. I missed you so much.
I don't really have time
because he's nearby
and he has a meeting.
So… Do you want to do this quickly?
Just… You know,
it'll just take a few minutes.
-He's somewhere nearby?
-Like old times?
Please?
Why are you dressing up?
Where are you going?
Madrigal?
Madrigal, come back!
Thanks for the help, Marlon.
Don't mention it.
By the way, where's Jepoy?
Wasn't he supposed to help you out?
You two had a fight, didn't you?
Fine, all right. We fought.
I don't get you men.
The moment the girl reciprocates,
you think she's ready to go all the way.
What do you mean?
You know… All the way there.
Whatever.
[chuckles]
Oh, "there." Okay.
That's just how guys are.
It's no big deal.
So, you admit that's
what all men think about?
Well, not every guy.
But that's what makes men
and women different.
Tell you what, Anna.
Just talk straight up to Jepoy.
I'm sure you two will figure things out.
[soft music playing]
If we catch the Big Four
and Emilia Ardiente,
that will be our biggest arrest.
All the ringleaders
and their factions here
in the Philippines will fall apart.
Then, we'll be able to find Red Dragon
and destroy all the syndicates.
It'll be one less problem
for Poblacion Ardiente.
After that, Diego can come back to me.
We have a problem, Governor.
The Dragon Ladies won't accept our bribe
in exchange for our gambling dens.
Especially now that Emilia's their leader.
Oh.
Emilia…
What is this?
I mean…
Why won't the Dragon Ladies
accept my bribe in exchange
for my gambling dens?
Well, we're not surrendering
that piece of territory
because it's one of
our biggest moneymakers.
In case you've forgotten…
That place used to belong
to the Ardientes.
And in case you've forgotten, Papa,
Mama snatched it away from you
when you weren't governor,
so you can't take it away from me.
[chuckles]
Well, would you look at that.
Now, that you're finally on top…
You've become so full of yourself.
Come on, Papa.
Spare me the drama. You're such a downer.
I have a meeting later with my colleagues.
Why don't you come with me?
Maybe then you'll understand.
Excuse me.
A meeting, huh?
Okay.
Looks like these pesky little
syndicates aren't going to stop.
They're the bane of my existence.
Well…
The lion is not going to sleep
until he puts this pesky
flock of sheep down the drain.
Magbanua.
You are about to watch an actual battle
planned in the true form and art of war.
Watch.
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
-There you go, Daddy.
-Thank you.
So, how do I look?
You'll be perfect in about now.
There you go.
[suspenseful music playing]
Let's go.
-I'll see you later, Daddy.
-Okay. I'll see you later. Bye.
Bye, Daddy. Bring home the bacon.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Julio] Wherever it is, you're not going.
No, Papa! The lion
is envious of the lioness
because you know that after that meeting,
I'll become even more powerful than you,
and you don't want that. I know you.
[gunshots]
Just make sure you're loyal to Emilia.
Otherwise, you'll get something
far worse than that.
Make sure nothing bad
happens to my daughter.
Diego, we're here.
-Something doesn't feel right.
-[gunshots]
Let's go.
[Arnaldo] You killed the old Arnaldo.
But now that my memories are back,
I will make you pay.
[theme music playing]